Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
No!
My god! God! No! Please!
- Shh! Enough!
- No. please!
- Just behave!
- No!
Damn it!
What the hell. Alice?
Damn it. Josh!
- Stay in character!
- Well. I'm sorry!
I just didn't expect you to get so rough!
Is my nose bleeding?
- No. it is not bleeding.
- Damn it.
It's definitely gonna bruise.
I have to present to clients on Monday.
This was a stupid
idea. Let's just forget it.
No. no. Wait. wait. wait. wait.
I've got this. Let me try again.
I'm gonna ravage you.
Gross.
Well. I'm sorry.
Do not apologize.
It came from Susan's house.
- Call 911.
- Josh. no.
Let the cops handle it.
Just stay here. okay?
Susan?
Susan!
Are you all right?
If there's anybody in
here. cops are on the way!
Susan granwell. dead in the kitchen.
Must have been a pretty
big donor for the mayor
to ask you all to step in.
They were old friends.
What do we know?
Neighbors heard a
commotion around 11:00 P.M.
One of them came to check on Susan.
found her bleeding out on
the ground. already deceased.
Preliminary cause of death is
blunt force trauma to the head.
Looks like she got hit with that cast iron.
Okay. we'll have it sent to
the lab for further processing.
Whose firearm is that?
Registered to the victim.
but csu didn't recover any shell casings.
So she wasn't able to
fire it off before she got hit.
That skillet's a weapon of opportunity.
so it's not premeditated murder.
What. a robbery gone wrong?
She confronted them with a gun.
they retaliated by grabbing a cast iron?
Maybe.
Nice house. lots of valuables.
Doesn't feel like a break-in.
Only disturbance was in here.
Windows and doors were
intact. Alarm didn't go.
Whoever did this either
had access to the house.
or she let them in.
Looks like a crime of passion.
I have a feeling Susan
granwell knew her killer.
All right. folks. last night. Susan granwell
was attacked and killed in her home.
a $12 million historically
preserved home in fields ton.
Susan was a major donor
and confidant of the mayor.
He would like her killer
brought to justice immediately.
Right. hey. have we
notified the family yet?
No... her son Bobby is in
Tokyo with his grandparents.
and because of the time change.
we haven't been able to reach them.
But by the time I have to
look this boy in the eyes
and tell him his mother is gone.
I would like to have
some real answers for him.
Our team's initial assessment was that
this looks like a crime of passion.
so let's talk about Susan
granwell and anyone
in her life who could have
snapped and killed her.
Right. well. Susan grew up
an Upper East Side socialite. old money.
Now she's a hotelier by way of marriage.
Her late husband. Alex.
founded a chain of boutique hotels
called the granwell hotels.
They have locations across the country.
Yeah. Sam and I
stayed at a granwell once.
They had a pillow menu.
Well. that's not all they got.
Turns out granwell hotels is knee-deep
in a serious labor dispute.
Maintenance and hospitality workers
have been on strike
for the past three months
with no end in sight.
They claim Susan is
trying to starve them out.
The protests have been peaceful.
but it's getting nasty.
Nasty enough to attack
Susan in her own home?
She thought so.
Susan filed a police report last week
after a brick was thrown
through her front window.
She blamed her disgruntled employees.
but the cops weren't
able to ID a suspect.
So the brick was to
scare her into returning
to the negotiating table.
When that didn't work. maybe
they amped up the intimidation.
and it got out of hand.
Who's running this union?
That would be Jeremy
Payton. career labor organizer.
known for running
campaigns of intimidation.
He has threatened multiple times
to burn down granwell properties.
Not the type to catch flies with honey?
Definitely not.
Granwell sent their goons to
rough me up. to silence me.
We're not scared of you!
You hear that. Susan?
You should be scared of us!
Well. he might be a charmer.
but if it walks like a motive
and talks like a motive...
well. forensics might back it up.
Yeah?
Report from the crime scene just landed.
and Jeremy's fingerprints
were found all over it.
Low lipid oxidation
in the residue suggests
his prints were recent.
- What about the murder weapon?
- Wiped clean.
No fingerprints there.
Well. nice try. Jeremy.
The man was there.
Let's bring him in.
Granwell. granwell. you can't hide!
We can see your greedy side!
- We can see your greedy side!
- Back up. scabs!
Nobody's getting through this picket line!
Get out of here! Boo!
Scab!
Excuse me. FBI. Excuse us.
Jeremy Payton. how you doing?
Why don't we take the
temperature down a little bit?
Law enforcement protecting
the corporate fat cats again!
Why am I not surprised?
No. No. wait.
That's not what's happening here. okay?
Look. Mr. Payton. we have
a few questions for you.
so why don't you come with us?
Obstructing a federal
agent is a crime. fellas.
So move. Now.
You don't tell them
what to do. sweetheart.
Sweetheart?
Okay. yeah. no. that's not gonna work.
Let's go.
You two. step aside. or you're coming.
Let's go. Hands behind your back.
See? You see what they're doing to us?
Don't let these jackboots
take away your voices!
Union strong!
You hear that. Susan?
You should be scared...
from the moment I saw you guys.
I knew that this was what it was about.
That's not what you were screaming
at your union brethren about.
You wanted them to
believe that we were there
to shut down your picket.
I saw an opportunity to
keep my people angry.
energized. and I took it.
Sure. it was theater. but so was this.
Nothing I said on that video was real.
So granwell hotels never sent you
their people to beat you up?
Not physically. but you know.
they've been beating
us down for long enough.
Jeremy. please. stop.
All right? That's enough.
Did you fake these injuries.
file a false police report
blaming Susan
granwell's private security?
You gotta give them an
enemy to keep them motivated.
So yeah. I had a couple
of my boys rough me up.
Blamed it all on management.
Sounds like a felony.
Well. it worked.
Momentum's on our side now.
So if Susan granwell is losing.
why'd you pay her a visit?
Your fingerprints. they're
all over Susan's home.
Doorknobs. kitchen counters.
Question is. are we gonna
find them on Susan's body?
Hold up. her body?
- You killed her.
- Wait. I...
beat her to death and
then fled. did you not?
Whoa... what are you talking about?
No. no. no. no. no. I didn't...
what? No.
No. no. susie.
That's my susie.
Your susie?
I didn't do this. I would never.
I mean. we... we
couldn't come out publicly.
but we were in love.
This woman was your sworn enemy.
You trash talked her daily.
For show.
From the second we met
at negotiations. I felt a spark.
We... we were the same. stubborn.
We wanted big things. you know?
We just chose different paths.
But that didn't stop the fates
from bringing us together.
It's a good story. but you know.
you've also proven
that you're a good actor.
It's not acting.
Prove it.
I proposed. How about that?
With my nan's heirloom ring.
You can check the
pics on my cell phone.
There's proof there.
I didn't do this!
I...
hey. Take a look at that.
Happy family.
Doesn't mean he's innocent. though.
No. but his alibi does.
The joc confirmed via security cams
that Jeremy was at the union office
at the time of the murder.
Well. he's also claiming that
the two of them were engaged.
so that would explain his fingerprints
all over Susan's house.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. but
that engagement ring.
that seems to be missing.
So what. you're saying that this
could be a robbery after all.
and Susan was killed over a ring?
It's possible. right?
Yeah.
I looked into vintage
rings like this for Nina.
and a rock like that from
the '20s. good clarity.
thing would go for 750k easy.
Thanks. Elise. Well. you win.
but by "price is right" rules.
Jeremy's insurance policy
puts the ring's value at 800k.
Okay. yeah. someone might kill over that.
- Yeah. for sure.
- Okay. but Jeremy said
that only the people in this photo
knew about the engagement.
Well. that's not entirely true.
Someone took this picture.
All right. so according to Jeremy Payton.
Bobby's private math tutor
took this photo. which means.
if true. this tutor is the
only other person we know
knew our victim had an $800.000 ring.
- Which is now missing.
- Right.
And Jeremy also said the tutor
had a key to Susan's home.
So that is means. that is opportunity.
and that's me hoping you
figure out who this tutor is.
Lucas Williams. 18.
lives in corona with his dad. frank.
and younger sister. faith.
Okay. Ian. you wanna
get up on his phone?
- On it.
- Any criminal history?
- Not even a parking ticket.
- He's an impressive kid.
Was up for the Miller-dier prize
in high school computing last year.
He's an honor student at the
Augustus school in Manhattan.
Yeah. a corona kid at a
private fancy school uptown.
Full ride. need-based scholarship.
Looks like dad's been
unemployed for a couple years.
Maybe he was sick of being the poor kid
at the country club school.
Right. saw an opportunity for a payday.
but then Susan caught him.
And. I mean. yeah. maybe.
Could be my bias
'cause he's my son's age.
but I'm having a hard time believing
this kid is our killer.
We need to talk to him.
- How we doing. Ian?
- His phone is dark. not just off.
Lucas must have taken out the battery.
He's savvy.
So he could be trying to not be found.
Hey. Augusta school counselor said
Lucas didn't show up today.
And his dad isn't answering.
All right. let's get a team
to Lucas Williams's house.
Straight ahead.
It's open.
Bedroom's clear.
Oa. I got a body.
Is it Lucas?
It's frank Williams.
You think Lucas did all this?
Killed his father?
If he did. it's his second
murder of the day.
Hey.
Do we have any bolo
hits on Lucas Williams yet?
No. no. but Elise is working on bringing
his sister. faith. in.
See if he knows what her brother's up to.
Someone has to.
I mean. 18. no criminal record.
full ride at a great school.
I mean. seemingly happy family.
Maybe I get killing granwell for the ring.
Yeah. I don't know.
Why does a kid like
this go that far for cash?
And then go kill his father.
Wait. Ian just sent an me prelim over.
and it puts frank's time of death
at approximately 28 hours ago.
Okay. meaning Lucas's father was killed
before Susan granwell.
Maybe Lucas. he kills
his dad. and then he...
he needs cash to go on the run.
It's a theory.
I don't know. there's just
something big we're missing here.
Hey. did you track down the sister?
Not exactly.
Spoke to faith's school admin.
She didn't come in today.
We pinged her phone
to the family home.
She left it behind.
You're saying faith Williams
appears to be missing?
All right. put out an Amber alert.
Look. we don't know
if faith is an accomplice
or a hostage yet. but if she's
with Lucas. she's in danger.
Okay. we got a bolo hit on Lucas.
NYPD foot patrol lost him
on west Broadway and prince.
A lot of high-end
consignment stores down there.
Grab Maggie and oa.
We're on it.
Scola and Eva checked
the other two shops.
No sign of Lucas.
Okay.
Excuse me. FBI.
We're looking for this kid.
He might have been with his sister.
Have you seen him?
Surely have. but he was alone.
Had a gorgeous '20s vintage
piece. incredible setting.
The clarity on it?
But he couldn't explain the provenance.
I don't deal with creatively sourced items.
if you catch my drift.
No. we get it. You operate above board.
So how did the conversation end?
I told him he'd have better
luck at the tawdry pawn shop
down the street.
You just missed him.
Thank you.
- Maggie. there he is.
- Got him.
- Hey!
- He made us.
In pursuit of our suspect.
heading south on Mercer
towards spring.
Please. no.
Lucas. you're under
arrest for the murder
of Susan granwell and frank Williams.
- Got the ring.
- Please don't do this.
They took my sister. I
was just trying to save her.
They're gonna kill her.
- Come on.
- No. no!
Please! Don't do this!
They're gonna kill her!
Who... who took your sister?
I don't know who they
are. but I stole from them.
and they know. and
they're gonna kill her!
- Okay. all right. stop.
- Back up. What'd you steal?
Okay. there is this crypto phishing scam.
I saw it on Reddit.
Idea is. y-you send fake transfer links
to a ton of people.
Like. "click here to
secure your crypto account"
sort of thing.
And. if someone clicks on one.
then all the crypto from their digital wallet
gets drained into yours.
What are you doing.
man? You're a bright kid.
You got a scholarship.
This was not a smart move.
Hey. I know this is my fault. okay?
I know.
But the phishing scam was anonymous.
- I don't know how they found me.
- Well. they did.
so why would you do this?
I was desperate.
My dad got laid off a couple years ago.
He hasn't been able to find work since.
We were gonna lose our house.
Our heat kept getting
shut off! We needed help!
All right. well. how
much help did you need?
Because it must have
been a lot for these people
to come after your family.
I got a couple small bites. you know.
100 bucks here or there.
But then I got one big hit.
How much?
315.000 in Bitcoin.
I paid off our mortgage.
caught up on all the bills.
I still had. like. 17k left over.
- Okay. Okay.
- I thought I was saving us!
Yeah. well. okay.
So whoever you stole
from. they found you.
When I got home from school yesterday.
my sister was gone. and my dad...
they left a phone in my dad's hand.
and it had a text message.
It said I had to transfer
the Bitcoin that I stole
into their wallet by 5:00 P.M. today.
or they were going to kill my sister.
Your sister gets kidnapped
by these unknown people
you robbed. and you didn't
have enough money left over
to pay them back. so that's why
you went to Susan granwell's?
I remembered that I had a key.
Right. easy access to a
house full of valuables.
and stealing worked once.
But why did you kill Susan...
she wasn't supposed to be home. okay?
I was just gonna grab
stuff that she wouldn't miss.
But she was there. and...
and I tried to sneak out.
But it was dark. and I tripped.
and she found me. and
she... she had a gun!
All I could think is.
she's gonna shoot me.
and then my sister is gonna die.
So... so I panicked.
I panicked. and I hit her.
- You killed her.
- I didn't mean to.
I didn't.
You still took the ring.
Yes.
To save my sister.
Please.
You gotta find her.
All right. folks. listen up.
This is faith Williams.
Lucas's 15-year-old sister.
and if we believe his
story. faith is in real danger.
Can we confirm she's
being held for ransom?
We found the burner
phone in Lucas's bag.
- There was a ransom text.
- Okay.
We should believe this is real.
Okay. so "Lucas Williams.
we know who you are."
"We know what you did.
"Send the money you stole
to the following wallet address
"by 5:00 P.M. tomorrow.
or your sister dies." Right.
That qr code does
correspond to a Bitcoin wallet.
Well. that only gives us a few hours
to find these kidnappers
and save this girl.
I'm guessing we cannot track the phone
- that sent the ransom texts?
- Correct.
Kidnappers must be
using another burner.
All right. all right.
so let's just respond to the message.
Just open up the line of communication.
All right. start the negotiations.
and get proof of life.
That's what we're looking for here.
Let's see if we can
smoke these guys out.
What? No luck?
Phone's off. or they're
in a spot with no signal.
Either way. they won't see our message
until their phone's back online.
Right. okay. so what
about the wallet address?
- Can we track that?
- Tried. but it's brand new.
No activity to exploit.
But I can track the wallet
Lucas initially robbed.
I am assuming they are
owned by the same person.
So if I can trace that wallet's ip address.
cross-reference it
with other public data...
- bingo!
- Yeah?
The wallet Lucas phished is affiliated
with an exchange account
registered to a novarin systems.
Novarin systems. What
kind of company is that?
Officially. it consulting. but according
to an ongoing rico investigation.
novarin systems is
also a suspected front
for the New York clan of bratva.
You're kidding.
This kid accidentally
stole from the Russian mob.
In an absolutely banner
stroke of bad luck.
18-year-old Lucas Williams
unknowingly stole $315.000
from bratva. the Russian mob.
How did they even know
Lucas was stealing from them?
Yeah. that's... that's nagging at me too.
We're just getting into it. so...
we just arrested the boss
of the New York clan six months ago.
Do we know who is in charge now?
Yeah.
Elise. how we doing on that?
Yeah. organized crime
believe the new head
of the New York clan
of bratva to be this man.
- 54 years old. named...
- Andrei ovechkin?
How long has he been in New York?
Immigration says three months.
I'm guessing you've heard of him?
You could say that.
All right. so. you remember my old man
used to work for the
state department. right?
Right.
So he was stationed in Moscow
for a couple years when I was 12.
I went to the international
school over there.
You wanna take a wild
guess who my best friend was?
Oof.
You were only in Moscow for two years.
Yeah. Yeah. but you know.
andrei was. you know...
he was like a brother.
Even after my family
moved back to the states.
you know. we talked
as much as we could.
We had a whole plan. you know.
He was gonna move here.
He was gonna stay with me.
We were gonna open up a...
Private investigator business.
you know. get answers
for people left behind in the system.
I smuggled a vhs tape of
"Chinatown" into Moscow.
and we used to watch it all the time.
I kind of had a thing for '70s noir.
You still in contact with him?
No. I haven't talked
to him since I was 20.
The Soviet union collapsed.
You know. it was chaos.
He went dark.
Eventually. I found out he
had joined bratva to survive.
But his name hasn't popped up in years.
I figured. you know. he had been killed
with the trajectory he was on.
Seems he got his stars instead.
Well. his tenure as
boss will be short-lived.
I want a full-scale raid
on his base of operations.
We'll force his hand to give up the girl.
Respectfully. obviously.
bratva is good for this.
But with andrei. if they
sent him here from Moscow.
he means something to the organization.
and the powers that be are
watching. and he knows that.
All the more reason for
him to make a statement.
No one steals from bratva
on andrei ovechkin's watch.
I don't know. my gut is just telling me
that's not how he'd handle this.
You know. it's sloppy. and
he's anything but sloppy.
Jubal. an innocent girl's
life is on the line here.
We've gotta have
more than just your gut.
Are you sure you can be objective here?
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
- No. no. no.
No. my historical knowledge
of andrei isn't a blind spot.
If anything. it's an asset.
Okay.
How do you feel about
paying an old friend a visit?
Hi. I'm here to speak with andrei.
He's not taking visitors.
That's not how we treat
our friends. is it. mitya?
Jubal Valentine.
All right.
Or I should say. assistant
special agent in charge?
- Okay. Yeah.
- So you looked me up.
I... I'd be surprised if you
had recognized me that fast.
Your Russian accent is also memorable.
Okay.
Come.
We have much to discuss.
Yeah.
No clothes. no weapons. no wires.
If I didn't know any better.
I'd say you don't trust me. andrei.
The boy I knew.
the one who referred to
the rules as suggestions.
him. I trusted with my life.
You disappeared on me. man.
What happened. right?
Jubal. please.
I'm not so naive to
think this is a social call.
Yeah. Well. you're right.
Did your men abduct a 15-year-old girl
named faith Williams yesterday?
We did not.
I know about the stolen crypto wallet
that belonged to the bratva front.
And you guys have
no sympathy for thieves.
So I am speaking to
the FBI. not my old friend.
We both made choices.
Yeah. we were out some Bitcoin.
but I don't play games for small prices.
315k. that's not nothing.
To us? Please.
And look at the trouble
it's caused between the FBI.
the online exposure.
Online exposure?
Bratva's shame is now public.
Everyone know that boy stole from us.
His name. his address. the amount...
it's all posted online.
So this kid made a fool of you.
and you knew exactly who he
was and where you could find him.
Jubal. anyone knows how
much cash that boy is sitting on.
Why would I do that?
I knew it's gonna be
open season on the boy.
Andrei was telling you the truth.
The forum is called protect the block.
referring to the block chain.
So Lucas Williams was
doxxed on this forum.
He was.
The site tracks suspicious
crypto transactions...
anonymously. but I am
working on ID'ing them.
And cyber crimes had
no idea about this forum?
We don't have the manpower.
Crypto theft is the
wild west of cybercrime.
Fitting 'cause whoever runs this forum
claims to be a white hat hacker.
But this hacker. he.
what. deputized himself?
He thinks they're on the side of justice.
Yes. if they suspect
someone has stolen Bitcoin
from another wallet.
they expose the thief.
Tagline of the forum is.
"actions have consequences."
Right. a-and they flagged
Lucas Williams's scam.
posted his address. photos. all that.
And the exact amount that he stole.
Okay.
Well. that's an "x marks the spot"
for any criminal who wants to
grab 315.000 in stolen crypto.
And anyone with an
Internet connection can see it.
I guess that's what andrei meant
when he said it's open season.
I just unmasked our white hat...
Whitney kabialis. software
developer here in the city.
She might know more.
I did nothing wrong.
Doxxing isn't even a crime.
That kid stole the money.
I just caught him before you did.
No. Whitney. what you did
was set off a chain of criminal events
that led to two people being murdered.
including the abduction
of an innocent girl.
Faith Williams is 15.
She had nothing to do with this.
and now her life is being ransomed
for some stolen Bitcoin.
all thanks to your forum.
I hope you find the girl. I really do.
But I am not responsible for
what nutjobs do with my posts.
Legally. that is not true.
You will be charged
with accessory to murder.
kidnapping. endangerment of a minor.
What is it that you always say?
"Actions have consequences"?
- Now a good time?
- It's perfect.
Whitney here was just about to offer
her full cooperation. right?
Yeah. I'll help.
Terrific.
Meet FBI intelligence analyst Ian lim.
He's the one who
cracked your forum security
- and identified you.
- Shadow proxy?
Been trying to narrow down
who might have seen your post
with Lucas Williams' information.
but your site wipes all
incoming ip addresses.
- Yeah. volatile logging.
- There is no backup.
You must have the
kidnappers' wallet address. right?
Yes. it was included in the ransom.
You should be able to ID them
from the previous transactions.
New wallet. never been used.
So they know what they're doing.
What haven't I tried?
We have no other way to track
or even communicate with them.
This girl's life depends on it.
Sending crypto is the only real way
to elicit wallet activity.
Wait. I... sorry. I'm
trying to keep up here.
It sounds like you're saying the only way
to trace back to the kidnappers
is to actually send the Bitcoin.
Unless... We drop
something else in their wallet.
All right. I know I'm still
out here carrying cash.
but I think I understand
enough about crypto
to know you can't send a
text to a wallet address. right?
Correct. You can only send crypto.
But I can create a new digital coin
that we can send to
the kidnappers' wallet.
What. you can just create
a new cryptocurrency?
Anyone can. It takes five minutes.
You're out here printing money. bro.
Yeah. not really.
It'll be valueless.
Just need it to get the
kidnappers' attention.
May I present... "Proof of life first" coin.
Very smart.
The coin is the message.
and hopefully this will get
them to turn on their burner.
Exactly.
As soon as this coin appears
in the kidnappers' wallet.
it'll tell them that Lucas is only willing
to pay the ransom if
they prove that his sister
is still alive.
They turn on their burner to send proof.
So send it.
Kidnappers must have
seen Ian's "proof of life" coin
and turned their burners back on.
Just in time.
It looks like they are about to respond.
Okay. here we go.
Lucas. please give them the money.
They said they're gonna kill me
if you don't give them the money.
Okay. time stamp on that news clip
is from one minute ago.
Turn that station on.
Is that... yeah.
Yeah. that's live. We
can still save this girl.
Okay. so where are they holding her?
The burner that they're using
doesn't have GPS services on.
and they stripped all location
metadata from the video.
She's in a pretty nondescript room.
Hang on.
That structure is a
round masonry heater.
That kind of brick design
with a small firebox.
that's really unusual.
It's German style. circa 1900 to 1915.
You're up on 20th century
masonry now. moran?
I helped my uncle renovate
a building one summer.
Would you let the man cook?
Most owners ripped these out by the '90s
because of the city's updated
air pollution control code.
but the ones that didn't
need to file permits.
- Elise.
- Yeah.
There can't be many of those things left.
Searching department of
buildings records for section...
- 21.
- 21 masonry permits.
filtering by year and style.
Okay. And then there were four left.
Yeah. we'll split the team.
We'll narrow it down on the ground.
Okay. SWAT's still a few minutes out.
Maggie and oa cleared
the other two buildings.
So you've got a 50/50 shot with this one.
Just proceed with caution.
We're in the right place.
Confirmed. jubal. this is
where faith was being held.
Copy that.
It's almost time. We gotta go.
All right. I count two... armed.
- Any eyes on faith?
- Negative.
We gotta confirm that faith is on site.
Copy. Going right.
Go. go. go.
- Got him?
- Go!
Opcen. two male suspects
fleeing north on dupont.
black dodge challenger.
Couldn't get a plate.
Put out a bolo now.
So... so two kidnappers got away.
One was killed.
What about Lucas Williams's sister?
No. Eva and scola swept the property.
She was not there.
So we don't know if she's alive or dead.
No. but we're digging into the perp
that our team took down.
How we doing. Elise?
Yep. Simon brumel. 20 years old.
No gang affiliation. just
minor drug possession.
assault charges for a couple bar fights.
It's a big leap from drunk and disorderly
- to murder and kidnapping.
- Got something.
Simon wasn't affiliated.
but looks like his father was.
He's bratva?
Why are you sweating. man?
We'll be there.
- You lied to me.
- Go to another room.
Faith Williams' kidnappers.
they... they work for you.
You really thought I
wouldn't figure it out?
You're not that slick.
Do not mistake our history
for permission to disrespect me.
I'm starting to question
our history altogether.
What are you doing.
man? She is a child.
I did not order this.
No? We ID'd one of the kidnappers.
The name brumel ring any bells?
Brumel's boy does not work for me.
None of those kids do.
I heard whispers about these kids.
they're trying to make a
reputation. to get noticed.
Well. they did. just not
so much how they hoped.
And I found out only
after you came here.
I don't know where
they're holding the girl.
Prove it.
Help me save her.
Thank you.
Thank you. Robin.
You want some?
Still eating like a 14-year-old. I see.
Old habits. I know.
It'll be the death of me.
Trust. jubal.
I asked these kids to meet.
They'll come to me.
Andrei's intel helped
us identify these two men
as our kidnappers... nikita
kharkov and ilia marinov.
They're practically kids.
If they spook and they don't
show up. we have nothing.
Having a face-to-face with
andrei means something.
If they're trying to move
up. this is their chance
to impress the boss.
They think recovering andrei's 300k
will make them invaluable to bratva.
Okay. jubal's wire is hot.
He and andrei are gonna get
them to incriminate themselves.
then we will arrest them
and use that information
to see if we can get
faith Williams' location.
Andrei could have
something planned here.
Are we sure we trust him?
No.
Showtime.
Hey. jubal. we have a car pulling up now.
Is it the black dodge we
last saw the suspects driving?
No. it's a green BMW.
Okay. we got a problem.
Nikita's the only one that showed up.
That means that ilia might be with faith
at a different location.
I think it's gonna put her in danger
if we arrest nikita here.
What I think you should do is get nikita
to say the location
where they're holding faith.
And whatever you do.
make sure that nikita
and ilia don't speak.
Here he comes.
Da. Da.
You wanted my attention.
You have it.
We figured out who robbed you.
Did I ask you to do that?
Do I know you at all?
No.
But I know you.
I could be an asset to you.
Make sure no one steals
from you ever again.
So where's my money?
I'll have it in... 90 seconds.
How... how much?
All of it.
315.000 in Bitcoin.
Is it me. or are you also
feeling a little doubtful here?
I mean. why is this...
why is he so confident
that the money's gonna come through?
I'm the accountant. Okay?
He is part of bratva. unlike you.
Answer his question.
We're not stupid. okay?
We have the sister as collateral.
You don't get your money
by 5:00 P.M.. we kill her.
Okay. well. I hate to break
it to you. but it's 5:00 P.M..
so where is it?
I see no money.
We'll show the thief we're serious.
- Ilia will finish the job.
- No. no. no.
No. no. stop. stop. stop. stop.
You kill that girl. my boss doesn't
get his money. all right?
You need to tell us where she is.
Hey. I said stop.
You need to tell us
where the girl is right now.
Let go of me! I can handle this. okay?
Enough.
Tell me where the girl
is before your stupidity
brings us all down.
The real men will clean up your mess.
You're gonna wanna check
how you talk to me. old man.
I'll be running bratva one day.
Kid... You will never be
a part of my organization.
Damn it.
Let me see. Let me see.
We need a medic in here!
- It's over. nikita.
- Get off me!
Where is faith Williams?
You better pray that that girl is still alive.
Where is she. nikita? Tell me!
Maggie. ilia is two blocks
north in the dodge challenger.
He has faith.
Copy. We're on our way.
Don't shoot.
She's in the trunk.
I could skip a round.
Okay. well. don't miss.
FBI! Drop your weapon!
Go. Go. go.
I got him.
Hey. faith.
You're okay.
Hey.
Where's Lucas?
Where's my brother?
I want my brother.
We've got him. faith. He's safe.
Come on.
- Is he okay?
- He's okay.
Such a tragedy. right?
Kid just made one bad
choice after another.
He was just trying to save his family.
Dad is dead. He's going to prison.
That girl is gonna end up in foster care.
I wish this one had a happier ending.
Yeah. me too.
They are both still young.
You know. with early parole
and the right support
system. maybe it's not too late
for Lucas to make different choices.
I'd like to believe that.
Yeah.
Some things never change. jubal.
I can hear you thinking from in here.
I couldn't tell if you were awake.
I am glad you're gonna be okay.
It'll take more than
this to bring me down.
Today was almost like the old days.
That's your idea of a good time?
Well. speaking of the old days.
I brought you something.
Remember our little
side business in Moscow?
Stealing pastila from the school comms
and selling it to the rich
kids at twice the price.
It was a nice little scheme?
Yeah.
We were always a good team.
Yeah. we were.
How long are you gonna
be in New York for. you think?
I'm sure someone in your
office can answer that for you.
It's not too late.
I know... I know it wouldn't be
exactly how we planned. but...
I could help you actually get out.
You have to work with
me. We can make it happen.
I know what you're saying.
I. too. am happy to see you again. jubal.
But...
Next time we meet.
I do not expect it will be as friends.
Get well soon. andrei.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today